

Jose Ortega

Contact information

Tel:

+57(301) 632 9479

Email:

josearmandoort@hotmail.com jose.ort98@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

/in/jose-ortega-13288b163/

Address:

Calle 22 # 26-13 Baranoa, Colombia

Summary

Software developer with experience in building scalable software platforms, based on open source technologies. High efficiency and knowledge of Flutter, Angular, Javascript and Java. Passion for user experience, ability to lead transition processes between development and design.

Education:

Universidad de la Costa CUC System Engineer, Ingenieria de Sistemas.

2017 - Present

Hobbies:







Experience:

Flutter Developer

Svnerio

01/2022 - 1/2023

- Responsible for the development and support of new mobile apps.
- Responsible for deployment.
- Lead the development of updates for the mobile app.

Software Developer

EUREKA TIC 02/2019 - 01/2022

- Responsible for the development, support, and deployment of mobile apps.
- Responsible for migration from native environments (IOS and Android) to Flutter.
- Lead the development of updates for the mobile app.
- Develop and implement microservices if necessary.
- Provide support for the company's products already deployed.

Bilingual support technologist

internally developed applications.

Atlantic International BPO 01/2017 - 02/2020

provide technical support to customers and agents, and be the first filter to validate a bug report with

References

Daniel Romero

- Software Architect.
- Agencia Nacional de Hidrocarburos (ANH).
- +57(300) 647 2112

Andres Lopera
- FrontEnd & Mobile Developer

- DANE.
- +57(312) 490 4222

- **Aaron Cunningham** VP of Software Development
- Synerio

aaron@aaronctech.com

Skills









Javascript













Others:





Materialize